Hello everyone and welcome to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎收听EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
My name is Catherine and today we're talking a little bit about going to sleep or not being
我是Catherine，今天我们聊一聊关于入睡或者睡不着的话题。
able to sleep.
无法入睡。
That's right.
没错。
We are having some sleeping problems and we're actually going to check out a couple of words
我们遇到了一些睡眠问题，现在我们要在“词汇预览”环节看看几个相关的词。
related to this topic right now on Vocabulary Preview.
词汇预览。
Vocabulary Preview.
Okay, so the first word is actually the technical word that describes being unable to sleep.
好的，第一个词其实是描述无法入睡的专业术语。
It's called insomnia.
它叫失眠症。
Right.
对。
So if you have insomnia, it means that you can't fall asleep.
所以如果你有失眠症，意思是你无法入睡。
You can't sleep.
你睡不着。
Okay.
好的。
So this is a pretty serious condition.
所以这是一种相当严重的情况。
For example, if you have insomnia and you don't sleep for three or four nights, you're
比如，如果你有失眠症，连续三四个晚上不睡觉，
not going to do very well at work, right?
你在工作上肯定表现不好，对吧？
Right.
对。
Or if you're studying, you're tired at school, you can't concentrate.
或者如果你在学习，在学校里会很累，无法集中注意力。
So it's a very big problem.
所以这是个很大的问题。
What's that other word though?
那另一个词是什么呢？
We have insomnia, but we also have another interesting disorder.
我们有失眠症，但还有另一种有趣的障碍。
Right.
对。
If somebody is able to sleep but walks while they're sleeping, that person is called a
如果有人能睡着，但睡觉时会走路，那个人就被称为
sleepwalker.
梦游者。
That's right.
没错。
And you don't actually just have to walk to be a sleepwalker.
而且梦游者不一定只是走路。
You can do any number of strange things like basically acting like you're awake when you're
你可以做各种奇怪的事情，基本上就像醒着一样行动，但其实
not.
你并没有醒。
Exactly.
正是。
So some people get up and walk, actually go outside.
所以有些人会起床走路，甚至走到外面。
Some people get dressed.
有些人会穿衣服。
Some people go downstairs and cook.
有些人会下楼做饭。
Yeah, that's right.
是的，没错。
And the worst is the people who eat because they gain weight and they don't know why.
最糟糕的是那些吃东西的人，因为他们会发胖，却不知道原因。
Exactly.
正是。
So sleepwalking is what you do.
所以梦游就是你所做的事情。
And if you do this, you're called a sleepwalker.
如果你这样做，你就被称为梦游者。
Okay.
好的。
Sleepwalk is the verb.
“梦游”是动词。
Sleepwalker is the noun or the person.
“梦游者”是名词，指人。
All right.
好的。
So we've taken a look at two words that we're going to find in our dialogue today.
我们已经看了两个今天对话中会出现的词。
Why don't we go now and listen to the dialogue for the first time.
我们现在为什么不先去听一遍对话呢？
Alex, what's up with you?
Alex，你怎么了？
You look dreadful.
你看起来糟透了。
Hey, Jill.
嘿，Jill。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I've been having trouble sleeping these past few weeks.
过去几周我一直睡不好。
I usually lie in bed for hours trying to get to sleep.
我通常躺在床上几个小时想入睡。
I've tried stretching and different breathing techniques before going to bed.
我试过睡前拉伸和不同的呼吸技巧。
I've tried eating and not eating different foods.
我试过吃或不吃不同的食物。
I've even tried counting sheep.
我甚至试过数羊。
And then when I finally get to sleep, I have these really disturbing nightmares.
然后当我终于睡着时，又会做非常令人不安的噩梦。
So I usually wake up in a panic and more tired than before I went to sleep.
所以我通常会在恐慌中醒来，比睡前更累。
Wow.
哇。
Maybe you should get that checked out.
也许你应该去检查一下。
Maybe you're stressed.
也许你压力太大了。
Just take some sedatives.
吃点镇静剂吧。
Works for me.
对我挺管用的。
Every so often having some melatonin on hand helps me when I have trouble sleeping.
偶尔手边备点褪黑素，在我睡不好时会有帮助。
It works on all kinds of sleeping disorders.
它对各种睡眠障碍都有效。
It's the stuff pilots use to regulate their sleeping patterns.
这是飞行员用来调节睡眠模式的东西。
I heard of that.
我听说过那个。
But does that apply to Alex's situation?
但那适用于Alex的情况吗？
Yeah, sure.
是的，当然。
Why not?
为什么不呢？
Sounds like he only has transient insomnia since it's a recent thing so taking melatonin
听起来他只是有短暂性失眠，因为这是最近才出现的，所以吃褪黑素
should do the trick.
应该能解决问题。
But shouldn't he be looking into why it's been happening?
但他不应该查查为什么会这样吗？
Well, aren't you the little psychologist?
哦，你还真像个心理医生啊？
Our buddy's having trouble sleeping.
我们的哥们儿睡不好觉。
It's easy and curable.
这很容易解决，也能治好。
It's not something freakish like if he was a sleepwalker.
又不是像他梦游那样怪异的事情。
Well, there's that too.
嗯，那倒也是。
Alright we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So obviously this person not only has insomnia but also has nightmares, sleepwalks, a mess.
所以很明显这个人不仅失眠，还有噩梦、梦游，一团糟。
That's right.
没错。
And you can tell when someone hasn't been sleeping well.
你能看出一个人没睡好。
They have that look like there's bags under their eyes or they just look really tired.
他们看起来就像眼睛下有眼袋，或者就是很疲惫的样子。
And so the friend here says, Alex, you look dreadful.
所以这里的朋友说，亚历克斯，你看起来糟透了。
That's right, dreadful.
没错，糟透了。
So this is an adjective and it's a way to describe someone that looks terrible.
这是一个形容词，用来形容某人看起来状态很差。
You look horrible.
你看起来糟糕极了。
You look tired.
你看起来很累。
You look sleepy.
你看起来很困。
That's right.
没错。
So this is not a compliment.
所以这不是一句赞美。
This is something that you say when you're worried about someone.
这是当你担心某人时说的话。
So for example, if someone's really, really tired, you say, you look dreadful.
比如，如果有人非常非常累，你会说，你看起来糟透了。
Or if someone is wearing very dirty clothes, they don't look like they went home yesterday,
或者如果有人穿着很脏的衣服，看起来像昨晚没回家，
you say, what's wrong?
你会说，怎么了？
You look dreadful.
你看起来糟透了。
Right.
对。
I think you can also use it to describe objects or maybe food, right?
我觉得你也可以用它来形容物品或食物，对吧？
This lasagna is dreadful.
这份千层面糟透了。
It means it's very bad.
意思是它非常难吃。
And you don't want to say that to the person who cooked it, of course.
当然，你不会对做饭的人这么说。
Exactly.
正是。
Alright, so the person obviously because is suffering from insomnia looks dreadful.
好了，所以这个人显然因为失眠而看起来糟透了。
And he was explaining what he does to try to fall asleep.
他解释了自己尝试入睡的方法。
For example, counting sheep, stretching, and he also said that he tried different breathing
比如数羊、拉伸，他还说试过不同的呼吸
techniques.
技巧。
Okay, so basically a technique is an approach to something, a kind of method.
好的，所以技巧基本上是一种做某事的方法或方式。
But in this case, we're talking about breathing techniques.
但在这里，我们说的是呼吸技巧。
So for some people, one breathing technique is breathing in through your nose and breathing
对有些人来说，一种呼吸技巧是通过鼻子吸气，然后
out through your mouth.
通过嘴巴呼气。
Like that.
像这样。
That's one kind of technique.
这是一种技巧。
So a technique, as you say, is a way of doing something.
所以技巧，如你所说，是一种做事的方式。
So breathing techniques are different ways of breathing.
所以呼吸技巧就是不同的呼吸方式。
So maybe you will relax, so maybe you'll fall asleep, things like this.
这样你可能会放松，然后可能入睡，诸如此类。
Exactly.
正是。
It's one of those things that you might learn about in a yoga class, for example.
这是你在瑜伽课上可能会学到的东西之一，比如。
There's different breathing techniques.
有各种不同的呼吸技巧。
Right.
对。
And you can combine techniques with other words as well, adding the ing.
你也可以把技巧和其他词组合起来，加上ing。
For example, you have walking techniques, maybe to put less stress on your knees.
比如，有走路技巧，可能为了减轻膝盖压力。
Or running techniques, swimming techniques.
或者跑步技巧、游泳技巧。
I think there's a technique for almost everything.
我觉得几乎每件事都有技巧。
Just about anything you can do, there's a technique for it.
几乎任何你能做的事，都有对应的技巧。
Right.
对。
Yeah, yeah, for sure.
是啊，是啊，确实。
All right.
好的。
And well, moving on, he was talking about his nightmares and he described his nightmares
然后，继续往下，他谈到了自己的噩梦，并形容他的噩梦
as disturbing.
令人不安。
He has disturbing nightmares.
他有令人不安的噩梦。
Okay, well, I think this is an important word to cover here, Marco, because we've heard
好的，我觉得这是一个需要讲解的重要词汇，马可，因为我们之前听过
the verb to disturb before.
动词“打扰”。
Like I'm sorry to disturb you.
比如“抱歉打扰你”。
It means I'm sorry to bother you.
意思是“抱歉打扰你”。
But disturbing is an adjective.
但“令人不安”是形容词。
It describes something that makes me very uncomfortable.
它描述的是让我非常不舒服的东西。
Right?
对吧？
Right.
对。
So, for example, a lot of times in the news, we see very disturbing images, car accidents
所以，比如，新闻里经常看到非常令人不安的画面，车祸
or fires or bombs.
或火灾或炸弹。
And what's disturbing is when you see human beings who have been hurt.
令人不安的是当你看到人类受伤的情景。
So images that make you really uncomfortable or sad, these are disturbing.
所以那些让你非常不舒服或难过的画面，就是令人不安的。
Exactly.
正是。
So disturbing nightmares are nightmares that are not very pleasant.
所以令人不安的噩梦就是不太愉快的噩梦。
They make him scared, maybe, or uncomfortable.
它们可能让他害怕，或者不舒服。
Right.
对。
Like a dream, for example, where your parents die.
比如一个梦，你父母去世了。
It's pretty disturbing.
这相当令人不安。
Exactly.
正是。
All right.
好的。
And well, one of his friends recommended, you know what?
然后，他的一位朋友建议，你知道吗？
Stop with all of this.
别搞这些了。
Just take some sedatives.
直接吃点镇静剂吧。
Okay.
好的。
So sedatives are a kind of medicine that help a person relax or that help make a person
所以镇静剂是一种帮助人放松或让人
tired.
疲劳的药物。
Right.
对。
So I think it comes from the verb to sedate.
我觉得它来自动词“镇静”。
Yes.
是的。
And basically that is to calm down, to tranquilize.
基本上就是让人平静下来，镇定下来。
That's right.
没错。
So in this case, we're talking about a person, but you can also give an animal sedatives.
所以这里我们说的是人，但你也可以给动物用镇静剂。
For example, if you want to take your dog on an airplane, the dog needs to relax.
比如，如果你想带狗上飞机，狗需要放松。
You give it some sedatives.
你给它一些镇静剂。
Exactly.
没错。
And I think when he mentioned a specific name of a sedative, it's melatonin.
我想他提到一种具体的镇静剂名称时，说的是褪黑素。
That's right.
对。
So melatonin, melatonin is a chemical that our bodies naturally produce that help calm
所以褪黑素，褪黑素是我们身体自然产生的一种化学物质，能帮助我们平静
us down.
下来。
And so a lot of pharmaceutical companies or drug companies sell melatonin in a pill form.
很多制药公司或药品公司以药片形式出售褪黑素。
It's basically, it's a chemical that helps you relax.
它基本上是一种帮助你放松的化学物质。
Exactly.
没错。
So obviously if you take melatonin, you're going to feel sleepy or you're going to be
所以显然，如果你服用褪黑素，你会感到困倦，或者你会
very relaxed and you're going to fall asleep a lot easier.
非常放松，更容易入睡。
Well, hopefully.
嗯，希望如此。
Hopefully.
希望如此。
That's right.
对。
So, and well, the whole thing that we've been talking about, insomnia, sleepwalking, these
所以，我们一直在讨论的失眠、梦游这些
are called sleeping disorders.
被称为睡眠障碍。
Right.
对。
And remember, you might also hear the term sleep disorders.
记住，你可能也会听到“睡眠失调”这个术语。
They mean problems with sleeping.
它们指的是睡眠方面的问题。
So people who either cannot fall asleep or people who have bad dreams or people who sleep
所以，那些要么无法入睡、要么做噩梦、要么梦游的人
walk.
都是如此。
Exactly.
没错。
So a disorder is something of an illness or a condition that is not normal.
所以“障碍”指的是一种疾病或异常状况。
So for example, as you said, a sleeping disorder or a sleep disorder, it means that you're
例如，就像你说的，睡眠障碍或睡眠失调，意味着你
not able to sleep properly or normally.
无法正常或规律地睡眠。
But there are other kinds of disorders, right?
但还有其他类型的障碍，对吧？
Right.
对。
And many people have heard of eating disorders.
很多人听说过饮食障碍。
Okay.
好的。
So that's basically people who do not eat like everyone else.
那基本上是指那些不像其他人那样进食的人。
Exactly.
没错。
So that's what happens with a disorder.
所以这就是障碍的情况。
All right.
好的。
So we've taken a look at a lot of vocab.
我们已经看了很多词汇。
Now it's time for us to take a look at Fluency Builder.
现在是时候看看流利度训练了。
But before that, why don't we listen to the dialogue again?
但在此之前，我们为什么不先再听一遍对话呢？
Alex, what's up with you?
亚历克斯，你怎么了？
You look dreadful.
你看起来糟透了。
Hey, Jill.
嘿，吉尔。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I've been having trouble sleeping these past few weeks.
过去几周我一直睡不好。
I usually lie in bed for hours trying to get to sleep.
我通常躺在床上几个小时试图入睡。
I've tried stretching and different breathing techniques before going to bed.
我试过睡前拉伸和不同的呼吸技巧。
I've tried eating and not eating different foods.
我试过吃不同的食物，也试过不吃。
I've even tried counting sheep.
我甚至试过数羊。
And then when I finally get to sleep, I have these really disturbing nightmares.
然后当我终于睡着时，又会做非常可怕的噩梦。
So I usually wake up in a panic and more tired than before I went to sleep.
所以我通常惊慌地醒来，比睡前更累。
Wow.
哇。
Maybe you should get that checked out.
也许你应该去检查一下。
Maybe you're stressed.
也许你压力太大了。
Just take some sedatives.
吃点镇静剂吧。
Works for me.
对我挺管用的。
Every so often having some melatonin on hand helps me when I have trouble sleeping.
偶尔备点褪黑素，在我睡不好时很有帮助。
It works on all kinds of sleeping disorders.
它对各种睡眠障碍都有效。
It's the stuff pilots use to regulate their sleeping patterns.
飞行员就用它来调节睡眠模式。
I heard of that.
我听说过那个。
But does that apply to Alex's situation?
但那适用于亚历克斯的情况吗？
Yeah, sure.
当然适用。
Why not?
为什么不呢？
Sounds like he only has transient insomnia since it's a recent thing.
听起来他只是暂时性失眠，因为这是最近才发生的。
So taking melatonin should do the trick.
所以吃褪黑素应该能解决问题。
But shouldn't he be looking into why it's been happening?
但他不应该查查为什么会这样吗？
Well, aren't you the little psychologist?
哟，你还挺像个心理医生嘛。
Our buddy's having trouble sleeping.
咱们哥们儿睡不好觉。
It's easy and curable.
这很容易治。
It's not something freakish like if he was a sleepwalker.
又不是什么怪事，比如他是个梦游者。
Well, there's that too.
嗯，那也有可能。
All right, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So now we have three main phrases for Fluency Builder.
现在流利度训练有三个主要短语。
Why don't we start with the first one?
我们先从第一个开始吧？
Okay.
好的。
So you heard in today's dialogue an interesting phrase.
你在今天的对话中听到一个有趣的短语。
I don't know if it exists in other languages, but in English we say when you're trying to
我不知道其他语言里有没有，但在英语中，当你试图
fall asleep, there's a good technique to help you do so.
入睡时，有一个好技巧可以帮助你。
You count sheep.
你数羊。
Yeah, I think you see it in cartoons all the time.
是啊，我觉得在卡通片里经常看到。
A person is sleeping and over that cartoon's head is a little cloud and you see sheep jumping
一个人正在睡觉，卡通人物头顶上有一朵小云，你看到羊跳过
over a fence, right?
栅栏，对吧？
So yeah, basically there's a fence and you say one, two, three, and the process of counting
所以基本上，有一个栅栏，你说一、二、三，数数的过程
helps relax a person.
能帮助人放松。
And you fall asleep.
然后你就睡着了。
Right.
对。
So counting sheep, I guess you're not literally out in a field counting sheep.
所以数羊，我想你不是真的在田野里数羊吧。
You're just imagining sheep in your head and you're trying to fall asleep.
你只是在脑子里想象羊，然后试着入睡。
That's right.
没错。
Counting sheep.
数羊。
All right.
好的。
And well, one of his friends recommended that maybe he should go to a doctor.
嗯，他的一个朋友建议他也许应该去看医生。
And Jill said that by saying, maybe you should get that checked out.
吉尔说这话的意思是，也许你应该去检查一下。
Okay.
好的。
So to get something checked out, to get it checked out, this means to have a professional
所以“去检查一下”，意思是让专业人士
give you a suggestion or to have a professional look at something.
给你建议，或者让专业人士看看某个东西。
Exactly.
没错。
So maybe you should get examined.
所以也许你应该去检查一下。
Maybe you should go to the doctor.
也许你应该去看医生。
This isn't just about disorders, right?
这不只是针对疾病，对吧？
I mean, what if I have a sore tooth?
我的意思是，如果我牙疼呢？
I could say this.
我也可以这么说。
Right.
对。
So if you have a toothache, I would recommend, maybe you should get that checked out by my
所以如果你牙疼，我会建议，也许你应该让我的
dentist.
牙医检查一下。
Right.
对。
Or maybe if you have a bad rash, you know, your skin is very red.
或者如果你起了严重的疹子，你知道，皮肤很红。
I say, Marco, I think you should get that checked out by a doctor.
我会说，马可，我觉得你应该让医生检查一下。
Exactly.
没错。
So to get something checked, to get something examined by a doctor or a professional.
所以“去检查一下”，就是让医生或专业人士检查某个东西。
All right.
好的。
And the last phrase that we have for you.
我们为你准备的最后一个短语。
So last phrase we have today comes from a suggestion at the end.
今天我们最后一个短语来自结尾的一个建议。
The friend suggests taking melatonin.
朋友建议服用褪黑素。
And he says, listen, taking melatonin should do the trick.
他说，听着，服用褪黑素应该能解决问题。
Right.
对。
So if you end the phrase by saying, that should do the trick.
所以如果你用“应该能解决问题”来结束这句话。
Basically you're saying that should solve your problem, that should help you.
基本上你在说那应该能解决你的问题，那应该能帮到你。
Exactly.
没错。
So the trick, you don't have to think about what the trick is.
所以“trick”这个词，你不用去想具体是什么“trick”。
It's just a way of saying it should fix your problem.
这只是一种说法，表示它应该能解决你的问题。
So for example, when someone is fixing my car and they have one more thing to do and
比如，当有人在修我的车，他们只剩一件事要做就完成了，
it's finished, he says, the car mechanic might say, that should do the trick.
修车师傅可能会说，那应该能解决问题。
Right.
对。
That means problem solved.
意思是问题解决了。
Or maybe you're having, you want to hang a picture on your wall.
或者你正想往墙上挂一幅画。
So somebody puts a nail in the wall and that should do the trick and maybe that'll hold
所以有人在墙上钉了个钉子，那应该能解决问题，也许就能挂住
up the painting.
那幅画。
Done.
搞定。
Okay.
好的。
So that's a way of saying, that should solve the problem.
所以这是一种说法，表示那应该能解决问题。
This should be the solution.
这应该是解决办法。
That should be all.
应该就够了。
Okay.
好的。
So why don't we go back and listen to the dialogue one last time.
那我们不如回去再听一遍对话吧。
Alex, what's up with you?
亚历克斯，你怎么了？
You look dreadful.
你看起来糟透了。
Hey Jill.
嘿，吉尔。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I've been having trouble sleeping these past few weeks.
过去几周我一直睡不好。
I usually lie in bed for hours trying to get to sleep.
我通常躺在床上几个小时都睡不着。
I've tried stretching and different breathing techniques before going to bed.
我试过睡前做拉伸和不同的呼吸技巧。
I've tried eating and not eating different foods.
我试过吃不同的食物，也试过不吃。
I've even tried counting sheep.
我甚至试过数羊。
And then when I finally get to sleep, I have these really disturbing nightmares.
然后当我终于睡着了，又会做非常可怕的噩梦。
So I usually wake up in a panic and more tired than before I went to sleep.
所以我经常在恐慌中醒来，比睡觉前还累。
Wow.
哇。
I think you should get that checked out.
我觉得你应该去检查一下。
Maybe you're stressed.
也许你压力太大了。
Just take some sedatives.
吃点镇静剂吧。
Works for me.
对我挺管用的。
Every so often having some melatonin on hand helps me when I have trouble sleeping.
时不时备点褪黑素，在我睡不好的时候能帮上忙。
It works on all kinds of sleeping disorders.
它对各种睡眠障碍都有效。
It's the stuff pilots use to regulate their sleeping patterns.
飞行员都用它来调节睡眠模式。
I heard of that.
我听说过那个。
But does that apply to Alex's situation?
但那适用于亚历克斯的情况吗？
Yeah, sure.
是啊，当然。
Why not?
为什么不呢？
Sounds like he only has transient insomnia since it's a recent thing.
听起来他只是暂时性失眠，因为是最近才开始的。
So taking melatonin should do the trick.
所以服用褪黑素应该能解决问题。
But shouldn't he be looking into why it's been happening?
但他不应该查查为什么会这样吗？
Well, aren't you the little psychologist?
嗯，你还真像个心理医生啊。
Our buddy's having trouble sleeping.
我们的朋友有睡眠问题。
It's easy and curable.
这很容易解决，也能治好。
It's not something freakish like if he was a sleepwalker.
这不像梦游那样怪异。
Well, there's that too.
嗯，那也是一种情况。
Alright, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So talking about dreaming, nightmares, insomnia, all of this, what do you do if you can't fall
所以谈到做梦、噩梦、失眠这些，如果你睡不着会怎么做？
asleep?
睡不着？
I don't really have this problem personally because I could fall asleep anywhere, anytime.
我个人没有这个问题，因为我随时随地都能睡着。
I've heard some people take like warm milk before going to sleep.
我听说有些人睡前会喝温牛奶。
Some people take milk, although I also heard that dairy products before bedtime can make
有些人喝牛奶，不过我也听说睡前吃乳制品会
you have nightmares.
让你做噩梦。
Oh, really?
哦，真的吗？
Like if you eat cheese before bed.
比如睡前吃奶酪。
I've heard that as well.
我也听说过。
I've heard that if you have seafood before bed, you'll have nightmares as well.
我听说睡前吃海鲜也会做噩梦。
But actually, have you ever had a dream when you are doing something and you wake up in
但说真的，你有没有做过那种梦，正在做某件事然后
the middle of that?
中途醒过来？
Yes.
有。
I remember once I was dreaming, I was drinking a soda and all of a sudden I woke up and I
我记得有一次我做梦在喝汽水，突然醒过来，发现
had my hand like in the air, like doing the action of me actually drinking the soda.
我的手举在空中，就像真的在喝汽水一样。
Actually sometimes this happens to me when I'm falling asleep.
其实我快睡着时有时也会这样。
I imagine I'm on a bike or something and I start to feel myself moving my legs and I
我幻想自己在骑自行车之类的，然后开始感觉腿在动，
wake up and I'm like, wait, wait, what am I doing?
醒来后就想，等等，我在干嘛？
So the brain is very strange, I think, especially in those times when you're kind of asleep
所以大脑很奇怪，尤其是在那种半睡半醒的状态下。
and you're kind of awake.
半睡半醒。
Also when you wake up suddenly, I don't know if other people have experienced this, but
还有突然醒来的时候，不知道别人有没有经历过，
you feel like you're falling or something, all of a sudden you just wake up with a shake.
感觉像在往下掉，然后突然惊醒，身体一抖。
Yeah, your body moves.
是啊，身体会动。
Yeah, it's really scary.
嗯，真的很吓人。
Your heart starts to beat.
心跳开始加速。
I don't know why that happens.
我不知道为什么会这样。
It's unusual.
这很不寻常。
Well, we're curious to know what your sleep habits are.
我们很好奇你的睡眠习惯是什么。
Do you have a hard time sleeping or are you like me?
你很难入睡还是像我一样？
It's very easy for you to fall asleep.
很容易就睡着了。
Let us know at our website, EnglishPod.com.
在我们的网站 EnglishPod.com 上告诉我们吧。
All right, we'll see you guys there.
好了，我们那里见。
Bye.
再见。